<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Aproximating Me]]></title>
  <link href="http://clokey.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://clokey.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-05-05T20:19:57+01:00</updated>
  <id>http://clokey.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Clokey]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alfred Workflows]]></title>
    <link href="http://clokey.github.io/blog/2014/05/05/alfred-workflows/"/>
    <updated>2014-05-05T20:12:44+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://clokey.github.io/blog/2014/05/05/alfred-workflows</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Now that I have some time on my hands, I&rsquo;ve decided to become more Ninja like with my keyboard fu. To that end I have thrown myself into using <a href="http://alfredapp.com">Alfred 2.0</a> a lot more. There are a whole host of really useful workflows published on the <a href="http://www.packal.org/">Packal</a> site and there are a large number of articles on useful and good workflows, that have really kicked started my used of Alfred.</p>

<p>I have also written my own workflow that binds ctrl+cmd+alt+F to toggle the functionality of the &lsquo;fn&rsquo; key on an Apple keyboard. Everytime the shortcut is executed it toggles the behaviour from default apple behaviour to <em>naked</em> functionality and vice-versa.</p>

<p>I have published the workflow on <a href="http://www.packal.org/workflow/toggle-function-keys">Packal</a> as well as put it my <a href="https://github.com/clokey/PublicCode/tree/master/AlfredWorkflows">PublicCode github repo</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bushey_monitor]]></title>
    <link href="http://clokey.github.io/blog/2014/03/27/bushey-monitor/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-27T20:48:28+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://clokey.github.io/blog/2014/03/27/bushey-monitor</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In 2010 I was intrigued about getting XBee mesh networks connected to twitter, it seemed to be the thing to do. As a result, I ended up purchasing an iDigi connectPort X4 starter kit, it came with an ethernet to XBee bridge and some indoor and outdoor temperature sensor.</p>

<p>The <a href="https://github.com/clokey/PublicCode/tree/master/bushey_monitor">result</a> is a small piece of Python, using the excellent BeautifulSoup, that responded to peoples requests for temperatures. As with the other code in the public repo, I am sure that the twitter api, no longer supports this interaction, but is here for pedagogic purposes.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[MacOSXVirtualSerialPort]]></title>
    <link href="http://clokey.github.io/blog/2014/03/08/macosxvirtualserialport/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-08T23:05:16+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://clokey.github.io/blog/2014/03/08/macosxvirtualserialport</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The first of the open source projects is now moved to the github repository. <a href="https://github.com/clokey/PublicCode/tree/master/MacOSXVirtualSerialPort">MacOSXVirtualSerialPort</a> was a means of creating a virtual serial port pair on Mac OS X 10.7. Sadly it doesn&rsquo;t work anymore as the code relied on an interface builder plugin that no longer works and an authentication model no longer supported in Mac OS X.</p>

<p>The readme file in the repo does include instructions on how to use the underlying socat tool to achieve the same outcome.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starting Over]]></title>
    <link href="http://clokey.github.io/blog/2014/03/08/starting-over/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-08T21:50:27+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://clokey.github.io/blog/2014/03/08/starting-over</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It&rsquo;s been a little over 5 years since I committed a great quantity of code to open source. A lot has changed since the
and the time is right to bring the code together on my github pages.</p>

<p>The plan is that as I migrate code over, I&rsquo;ll update this blog and provide links into the repository.</p>

<p>First up, Mac OS X Virtual Serial ports, a project that provided a wrapper around the socat command line tool
and has been broken for at least 2 releases of Mac OS X. I am not necessarily proposing fixing it right now, but at least bring bring it to github first.</p>

<p>Onwards.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
